everybody wanted the atat from the Star Wars wow it's a really exciting toy or is it yeah his legs moving that and
每个人都想要《星球大战》中的AT-AT玩具，真是令人兴奋的玩意儿啊！它的腿可以动，效果相当不错。
the 80s ones had guns that moved and lit up but you have to put your hand in to operate its head and
那些八十年代的玩具枪可以动并且还会发光，不过需要把手伸进去才能操控它的“头部”动作。
yeah the legs move if you operate them with your hands wouldn't it be better if it walked along now I'm aware of
是的，如果用手来操控这些腿部的话，它们就会动起来，那样不是更好吗？现在我知道了该怎么让它们移动了。
a walking at a tea toy
一个可以行走的AT-AT玩具
which was made by thinkway but this was quite a bit smaller and
这个产品是由Thinkway公司制造的，不过它的尺寸要小一些。
didn't really walk amazingly well mostly its feet are just sliding on the ground I suspect it had a similar mechanism to the
其实走起来并不怎么样，大部分时间都是脚在地面上打滑。我怀疑它的行走机制和……类似吧。
3D printed ones
3D打印的制品
that have been going around and ultimately that's because licensed toys cost a lot to produce so cutting down on Motors and
那些在市面上流传的玩具，之所以能够继续销售，是因为获得许可的玩具生产成本非常高，因此必须减少电机的用量。
control Electronics is generally how things go in the toy industry otherwise the product ends up costing too much I've built quite a
控制元件在玩具行业中扮演着重要角色，否则产品的成本将会过高。我制作了不少这样的元件。
few four-legged walking robots in the past I spent years through multiple versions of robot dogs before I got to something
在过去，我花了多年时间研究各种版本的机器人狗，直到最终找到了合适的解决方案。
that could move fast and was Dynamic but I actually started with bipedal robots like my the Star Wars gonk droid which
它移动得非常迅速，而且具有动态特性。不过实际上，我是从双足机器人开始的——比如《星球大战》中的那种笨拙的机器人。
walked Along on two legs at the time I thought if I can make something not too bad that walks on two legs
当时我心想，如果我能创造出一种并不糟糕、且只能用两条腿行走的生物的话……
and four legs should be easy but what I didn't consider was that the gong drop had big flat feet and
四条腿的组装应该并不困难，不过我忽略了一个问题：那个锣锤的脚部设计得相当笨重……
typically robot dogs have much smaller pointy feet which is why it took me so very many versions to make a robot dog
通常，机器人狗的脚都相当小，因此我需要经历很多次修改才终于造出了满意的机器人狗模型。
that walked well but I never went back to build a four-legged walking robot with big flat feet to see how easy that
那个机器人走起来很顺畅，但我从未再尝试去制造一个拥有四条腿、脚掌平坦的机器人，想看看制造这样的机器人到底有多简单。
would be and the at 80 is a great robot to convert because
“would be”……而AT-AT是一款非常适合进行改造的机器人，因为……
it's got these great big flat feet with these stabilizing toes I'm going to use a very similar parallelogram leg mechanism to the
它有非常大的扁平脚部，同时拥有能够提供稳定性的脚趾。我将使用一种与之前使用的平行四边形腿部机制非常相似的方案来解决这个问题。
gong Droid
笨蛋机器人
which had a gear reduction built into the leg I worked out the geometry for this in the gong Droid series which
该装置的腿部内置了减速机构。我在《Gonk Droid》系列作品中详细推导出了其结构设计。
you can check out in my channel essentially though it's a motor with a Spur Gear Running on a large partial gear and
不过，你可以查看我的频道哦。那里有一个带有副齿轮的电机，运行在一个较大的部分齿轮上。
as I demonstrated in the previous videos the large gear just needs to be the same radius as the top part of the
正如我在之前的视频中所展示的，大齿轮的半径应该与顶部的部分相同。
parallelogram and
平行四边形
then the gears track each other just fine instead of a DC motor this time I'm going to use some servos with a
那么，这些齿轮就能很好地相互配合了。这次我不会使用直流电机，而是会使用一些伺服电机来驱动它们。
gear mounted on the servo horn just a quick ad for my 3D printing sponsor thanks to lol's bar for supporting my Channel
安装在舵机臂上的齿轮装置——这里简单介绍一下我的3D打印赞助商吧！感谢LOL的Bar对我的频道给予的支持。
with 3D printers having lots of printers really helps get the projects done in time obviously we have to make four of everything
使用3D打印机显然有助于项目按时完成——我们当然需要为所有物品都准备四台打印机。
because it has four legs and in some cases that's actually more parts the legs themselves have four sections so
因为它有四条腿，而某些情况下，这些腿本身还包含更多的部分；也就是说，每条腿本身就有四个节段。
we have to make 16 sticks to make our four parallelogram legs and here's one of the gears that
我们需要制作16根杆子来构建我们的四个平行四边形腿。这是其中一个齿轮的示意图。
goes on the servo right all my parts are printed so
所有部件都已经打印出来了，现在就可以安装到伺服上啦。
we're ready to do some assembly thanks to 3D fuel for the filament for this this is all pro pla plus so
多亏了3D燃料技术，我们现在可以开始组装了。这一切都是出于对Pro Plus系统的信任才做的。
here are my gears for the servo there's a recess so that that
这是我为伺服电机准备的齿轮部件，那里有一个凹槽，可以用来固定齿轮。
gear can get really close to the servo body but obviously those little things sticking up are probably going to snap off it'll
齿轮可以非常接近伺服电机的机体，不过显然那些突出的小部件可能会脱落掉……
be okay though
不过，应该没问题的吧。
because the bulk of the gear is just fine the servo itself fits into a Servo bracket which is 3D printed and
因为大部分设备都运行正常，所以伺服电机本身可以放入一个通过3D打印机制作的伺服支架中。
yes I remember to leave the hole for the cable to come out just on the end there so
是的，我记得在电缆穿出的那个末端留了一个孔。
we can screw them in
我们可以把它们拧进去。
that bracket fits onto one of the pieces of the leg there and obviously there's a recess so that
那个支架可以套在腿部的某个部件上，显然那里有一个凹槽，以便安装时方便固定。
the gear can turn without binding on it
这个齿轮可以自由转动，不会受到任何限制。
the other side of the leg has that partial spur gear on and that binds nicely onto the gear that we've got so
腿的另一侧装有了那个局部凸齿齿轮，这个齿轮可以很好地与我们已经拥有的齿轮相配合。
now we just need to install something on each end so that we've got our parallelogram I've got some three millimeter steel axles
现在我们需要在两端安装一些装置，这样就能形成平行四边形结构了。我有一些三毫米厚的钢轴。
so now we can put together the parallelogram and now we've got a working mechanism with a motor in it so giving that
现在，我们可以组装出这个平行四边形结构了。这样一来，我们就拥有一个带有电机的实用机制了。
Servo a signal on some power we can see that moves quite nicely and that Servo tracks the big gear perfectly just because
我们看到，该伺服设备能够接收到信号后，会非常平稳地运行。而且，该伺服设备能够完美地跟踪那个大齿轮的位移。
the big gear is the same radius as the top part of the parallelogram so
大齿轮的半径与平行四边形顶部的部分相同，因此……
that's worked out well again really happy if how that's turned out there's hardly any slop in this as well so
事情又进展得很顺利啊！很高兴事情的结局如此美好。这个产品几乎没有浪费的成分，真是太好了。
it's actually quite a rigid mechanism so with these stages stacked together there's going to be hardly any wobble in the legs so
实际上，这个机制相当严格。由于各个阶段紧密衔接在一起，因此双腿几乎不会产生任何晃动。
all we need to do now is build the top of the leg and then build four more of them and
现在我们只需要制作出腿部的上部结构，然后再制作四个这样的部件即可。
put it all together so here's one whole leg with its two stages so it can bend in the middle so that
把它们组合在一起，这样就有了一条完整的腿，而且这条腿有两个阶段，可以在中部弯曲。
gives us quite a wide range of motion we've got a big enough stripe there to walk like an AT-AT and
这让我们拥有了相当广泛的动作范围。那里有足够的空间，可以像AT-AT那样行走。
of course we can bend the leg as well to pick it up so
当然，我们也可以弯曲那条腿来将其拾起。
if we Bend both Motors in the same direction then we can pick the leg up and that
如果我们同时让两个电机朝同一个方向旋转，那么我们就可以抬起那个部件了。
gives us enough ground clearance to take steps but before we put the rest of the parts for that
这给了我们足够的离地间隙，可以进行下一步操作。但在安装其余部件之前……
together it's time for a quick ad from the video sponsor which is curiositystream curiosity stream offers many award-winning documentary series that
现在，是时候为视频的赞助商——CuriosityStream做一下简短的介绍了。CuriosityStream提供许多获奖的纪录片系列节目……
you can't find anywhere else the content spans many factual topics including science technology engineering nature history food and lots lots more so
您在其他任何地方都找不到相关的内容，因为该内容涵盖了众多主题，包括科学技术、工程学、自然科学、历史、食品等等。
there's something for everyone curiosity stream plan starts at just five dollars a month you can choose a monthly or annual plan and
无论你喜欢什么风格的内容，Curiosity Stream的套餐都很适合大家——每月只需五美元即可开始使用。你可以选择按月或按年付费的套餐。
get access to thousands of hours of quality content and is available on multiple devices like your TV computer and also mobile devices
您可以访问数千小时的高质量内容，这些内容可以在多种设备上观看，包括电视、电脑以及移动设备。
so you can watch your favorite content on the go all content on curiosity stream is factual so
因此，你可以随时随地观看自己喜欢的内容。Curiosity Stream上的所有内容都是基于事实的，所以大家可以放心观看。
there's a big focus on education whether it's science technology or history the documentaries are informative and engaging obviously I really like science
这些纪录片非常注重教育内容，无论是科学、技术还是历史领域。这些纪录片信息丰富且引人入胜，显然我非常喜欢科学类的内容。
and technology so I really like the series called Engineering in the future which
以及技术方面的发展，因此我非常喜欢《未来的工程学》这一系列节目。
covers the metaverse hyperloop technology space exploration flying cars but also includes a documentary about Timber skyscrapers go to curiositystream.com jamesbrussin or scan
该内容涵盖了元宇宙、超级高铁技术领域的探索，还包括关于木质摩天大楼的纪录片。更多相关信息请访问curiositystream.com或扫描相关二维码。
the QR code for unlimited access to the world's top documentaries
无限访问全球顶级纪录片的二维码
and non-fiction series and for my fans use promo code James Bruton and you'll get 25 off so
还有非小说类系列作品！对于我的粉丝们，使用促销代码“James Bruton”即可享受25%的折扣哦。
click the link below or go to curiositystream.com jamesbroughton and save 25 right now right time to get back to the attacks so
点击下面的链接，或者访问curiositystream.com，然后立即节省25美元。现在就是行动的最佳时机，可以重新发起攻击了。
I made the whole thing four times so we've got four legs each one has two servos so
我把整个装置制作了四次，所以总共有四个关节。每个关节上都有两个伺服电机负责控制方向。
that's eight servos but then there's another four servos at the top and that's going to enable the robot to turn so
总共有八个伺服电机，不过顶部还有另外四个伺服电机，这些伺服电机将使机器人能够进行旋转操作。
we've got a plate that goes on the bottom and the top and I've just got some bolts which are put through there
我们有一个可以安装在底部和顶部的托盘，而我只需要一些螺栓来固定它罢了。
so we've got pivot Points and then we've got a Servo for each leg that
因此，我们有了旋转点，而且每条腿还配备了一个伺服系统。
runs on a larger gear on the top plate so that
在顶板上使用了更大的齿轮，这样就能实现更高效的运转了。
we can swing the legs outwards I thought it was a shame to tear the head and
我们可以将腿向外伸展。觉得把头部撕掉真是太可惜了……
body off the original at A T so I'm printing a new one and this is printed on the lolsbot Tas long bed
由于A T上的原件已经损坏，所以我正在打印一份新的副本。这份新副本被打印在Lolsbot的Tas长床上。
which has a really long bed for big parts so
它的床非常长，适合放置大型部件，因此……
my proportions aren't quite the same as the original toy but I'm pretty happy with the way it's turned out and
我的模型的比例虽然与原始玩具不太一样，但我对最终的成品效果相当满意。
I think mechanically it's going to be pretty solid the headphones printing right now but we're going to put some Electronics in so
从机械设计的角度来看，目前这些耳机的功能应该相当不错。不过，我们会加入一些电子元件来提升设备的性能。
as usual I've got an Arduino Mega that's more than enough to control those servos and
像往常一样，我拥有了一台Arduino Mega，这台电脑完全足以控制那些伺服电机了。
it's got this piece of strip board with all these wires broken out of it with power and
那块条形板上有一些电线断了，而且还缺少电源连接。
the signal distribution for the 12 servos it's got an RC receiver on it the orange thing on there that's because
该设备拥有12个伺服电机，配备了一个遥控接收器。那里有那个橙色装置，就是用来连接遥控器的。
we're going to be using my universal remote I made which is a DSM remote so check that out and
我们将会使用我自己制作的通用遥控器，该遥控器是DSM格式的遥控器，请务必检查一下吧。
my channel right let's uh try and get all this wired up so we've got all those Electronics installed and
我的频道准备好了，让我们试着把所有设备都接好，确保所有电子元件都安装完毕。
the cables rooted as best possible and zip tied on and we've also got the head installed the Arduino lives in there and
电缆被尽可能牢固地固定下来，然后用扎带绑紧。此外，头部装置也已经被安装好了。Arduino就安装在那个里面。
the main battery lives right at the back so I've just tied the controller to the servos for now so
主电池位于后方，所以目前我只是将控制器连接到了伺服上而已。
they all Bend in the same direction and you can see the whole thing goes up and
它们都朝同一个方向弯曲，你可以看到整个物体是向上移动的。
down as it bends its legs as you'd expect and also quite helpfully it can stand on one leg so
正如你所预期的那样，它在弯曲双腿时会向下倾斜。而且它还能用一条腿站立，这一点非常实用。
those stabilizing feet really help to keep it upright you wouldn't be able to do that
那些稳定的底座确实有助于保持设备的直立状态，否则的话就做不到这一点了。
with one of my open dog projects but it would just fall over in that
我的一个开源项目就存在这个问题，它在使用时经常会崩溃。
direction but in order to take steps with one foot at a time what we actually need is it goes forwards is all
方向很重要，但关键是一次只迈出一步。实际上，我们需要做的就是不断向前推进。
of the other feet to slide back in a perfectly straight line now this is actually quite a complicated mechanism here to do
其他脚现在可以沿着一条直线滑回去了。实际上，这是一个相当复杂的机制。
that and we're going to do it properly so
那样做的话，我们一定会好好地执行这件事。
we're going to calculate some inverse kinematics I did a more in-depth video about this before where I builds a simple robot arm
我们将要计算一些逆运动学参数。之前我制作过一个关于这个主题的深入视频，其中我构建了一个简单的机器人手臂模型。
the calculations I did for this allow me to position the end of the arm into Cartesian coordinates
我进行的计算让我能够确定机械臂末端的笛卡尔坐标位置。
that means up and down and left and
也就是说，可以向上、向下、向左、向右移动……
right in straight lines the code running calculates the required joint angles for the two joints I use Pythagoras Theorem and
代码直接计算了两个关节所需的联合角度。我使用了勾股定理来计算这些角度。
trigonometry to work out the angles the at 80 is very similar if we consider the leg to be a triangle so
通过三角学可以计算出各个角度。如果将AT-AT的腿部看作一个三角形，那么计算起来会非常方便。
first I worked out the angles from the required length of the leg which is easy because
首先，我根据腿所需的长度来计算各个角度，这很简单。
we know all three sides once this is done we can set the leg length and
一旦这一切完成，我们就已经掌握了所有必要的信息。接下来就可以确定各部分的长度了。
the code will work out the angles next we need to move the foot back and forth we can just imagine that
这段代码能够计算出各个角度。接下来，我们需要让脚来回移动，我们可以想象一下这个过程。
the leg is a straight line since we can set its length already so
由于我们可以预先设定腿的长度，所以这条线实际上就是一条直线。
we can imagine another right angle triangle where we give it the distance we want to move back and
我们可以想象另一个直角三角形，给这个三角形一个我们想要移动的距离，然后……
forth the height of the body and then use trigonometry to work out the shoulder angle and
从身体的最高点开始，然后使用三角学来计算肩部的角度。
the new leg length we pass the new leg length onto the previous calculation and
我们已将新的腿长数据应用到之前的计算中，然后……
then the body will stay at the same height as the foot moves back and
这样，身体在脚后退时仍然会保持与脚相同的高度。
forth the only thing I didn't take into account properly was this piece of the leg here because these two joints don't meet
我唯一没有仔细考虑的就是这里的那条腿的碎片，因为这两个关节并没有连接在一起。
so it's not a perfect triangle but I just ignored that and it works perfectly well so now we can actually move that
所以这并不是一個完美的三角形，但我并没有在意这一点，它仍然可以很好地发挥作用。现在，我们可以开始行动了。
body up and
站起来吧
down as we did before but instead of just moving those servos directly coupled to the stick we're actually calculating trigonometry and
我们还是采用之前的方法，不过不是直接控制那些与摇杆直接连接的伺服电机，而是实际上通过计算三角函数来操控它们。
working out the leg length and now I can pretty much slide backwards and forwards as well in a straight line so
现在我已经调整好了双腿的长度，可以自如地在直线上前后移动了。
if you look at the cabinet behind me you'll find that
如果你看我身后的那个柜子，你会发现……
body is tracking it at some point those servos do reach their end stops though and
身体正在追踪它，不过那些伺服电机最终还是会停止运转的。
also the cheap hobby servos have quite low tolerance feedback pots in probably about 10 tolerance so that
此外，那些价格低廉的业余级伺服控制器所使用的反馈电位器灵敏度相当低，大概只有10左右的灵敏度等级而已。
means you probably don't get a linear response out of them that along with the broken triangle at the knee means that
这意味着你可能无法从他们那里得到线性的响应。而且，膝盖处的那个“破损的三角形”结构也会影响到他们的表现。
we don't get a perfectly straight line in any direction but we've got enough that we can make it walk and
我们没有朝任何方向延伸出完全笔直的线条，但现有的线条已经足够让我们让物体能够移动了。
the legs move backwards and forwards in pretty much a straight line so we can take steps so
双腿沿着几乎直线的方向前后移动，这样我们就能迈步前进了。
obviously I can move the feet independently and
显然，我可以独立移动双脚。
we can put a step sequencer together to make it take steps you can see the foot doesn't track the ground perfectly but
我们可以组装一个步长控制器，让它按照你所设定的步数进行移动。不过需要注意的是，机器人的脚部可能无法完美地跟随地面移动。
it's good enough for our purposes there's one other issue we need to solve though if I move my hand along the table
这已经足够满足我们的需求了。不过还有另一个问题需要解决——如果我把手在桌子上移动的话……
here
这里
so it tracks in a perfectly straight line You'll see that my arm gets longer in this position and
因此，它的移动轨迹完全是一条直线。你会看到，处于这种位置时，我的手臂会显得更长一些。
it gets longer in this position as we move further away from the center but you'll also notice that
当我们远离中心时，这条线的长度会不断增加。不过你也会注意到……
my shoulder is moving a lot more than my elbow the elbow joint hardly ever moves and
我的肩膀移动得比肘部多得多，而肘关节几乎不动。
my shoulder makes most of the motion so
我的肩膀承担了大部分的动作负担。
if we were just to send the two servos of the leg to another position in a straight line like this then one
如果我们只是将腿部两个伺服电机的位置沿着直线移动到一个新的位置，那么其中一个……
has to move further than the other
必须比其他地方走得更远一些。
and if we just send them at the speed that the servos will go at which
- 如果我们以伺服电机当前的运行速度来操控它们的话……
is their maximum speed then basically one is going to get there first the other one will catch up later and that
那么他们的最高速度就是如此了。基本上，一个人会先到达那里，另一个人则稍后会追上他们。
means we won't be moving in a perfectly straight line anymore when I'm driving the joints manually effectively I'm scrolling through all the
这意味着，当我手动操控关节时，我们不会再沿着一条完美的直线移动了。实际上，我正在逐一检查所有的……
positions from A to B
从A到B的路线/路径
because I'm moving this thick quite slowly through all the positions over time and
因为我会逐渐、缓慢地将这个物体移动经过所有的位置。
the math is being calculated 100 times a second to work out the joint angles and
这些数学计算每秒进行100次，目的是确定关节的角度。
therefore the leg tracks in a straight line from point A to point B but if I was just to suddenly send a
因此，这条腿确实沿着直线从点A走向点B。不过，如果我突然……
step from one position to the next then those two joints will move them maximum speed
从某个位置移动到下一个位置，这样两个关节就能以最快的速度移动了。
and one will get there faster than the other so what we need is something that
其中一个人到达那里会比另一个人更快，所以我们需要的是某种能够加快这一进程的方法。
will manually scroll through all the positions but do it automatically when we specify two points and to do that
将会手动滚动所有位置，但当我们指定两个点时，会自动执行此操作。
we can use the Arduino ramp Library the simplest demo for that is specifying two points and then opening a Serial plotter and
我们可以使用Arduino的斜坡功能库来实现这个简单的演示。最简单的做法就是指定两个点，然后打开串行绘图工具，进而进行绘图操作。
seeing the interpolation between them which is a nice straight line instead of a square wave or a step that
看到它们之间的过渡是一条平滑的直线，而不是方波或阶跃函数……
new interpolated value is fed into the inverse kinematics so all the way through that value changing over time recalculates the joint angles
新的插值值被输入到逆运动学计算中，随着时间的变化，该值会不断重新计算各关节的角度。
and our feet move in a straight line from position to position I'm also using motion filtering on my control sticks and
我们的双脚也会沿着直线从一处移动到另一处。我还在控制杆上使用了运动滤波功能。
on the servos themselves on the output so
在伺服电机本身上，针对输出进行调节。
I made a video specifically about this you should check out where I made a robot head with really cheap servos and
我专门制作了一个关于这个主题的视频，你可以去看看。我在视频中使用了非常便宜的服务器来制作机器人头部部件。
controlled it with an 8-bit Arduino and you can see the Motions are really smooth there as I move around and
我使用8位Arduino来控制它，你可以看到当我移动身体时，动作非常流畅。
basically all I'm doing is taking a large percentage of the previous value in the loop and
基本上，我所做的就是在循环中取之前数值的很大一部分……
only a small percentage of the new ones so the values can't change too quick and
新注册的用户比例很小，因此这些用户的价值不会很快发生变化。
we get this lovely deceleration on the moves so
我们在移动过程中会感受到这种不错的减速效果。
now if I switch a switch on the controller we've got a timed sequence running that
现在，如果我打开控制器的开关，那么一个定时序列就会开始运行了。
lifts each foot in turn pretty much the way a dog walks if I push forward on one of my control sticks then
如果我对其中一个控制杆施加推力，那么每只脚的移动方式就类似于狗走路时的动作。
it takes the multiple of
需要乘以某个倍数
that control stick and moves all of the feet backwards which are on the ground and the one forward which
那个控制杆会让所有位于地面的脚部向后移动，而唯一向前移动的则是……
is off the ground and so it walks along pretty convincingly and
它已经投入使用，因此运行起来相当顺畅。
pretty much how an AT-AT walks flicking another switch causes it to lift diagonal legs and if I turn one of the controllers
基本上就像AT-AT的行走方式一样：按下另一个开关会导致它抬起对角线的“腿”。如果我转动其中一个控制器……
that causes the legs to swing out at the appropriate time to make it turn the legs don't share a common pivot point
这样就能在适当的时候让双腿向外摆动，从而实现转身动作。不过，双腿并没有共同的旋转点。
and that pivot point isn't in the middle of the robot which means the feet should actually move position in and
而那个旋转点并不在机器人的中央位置，这意味着机器人的脚实际上会移动到一个特定的位置。
out as it rotates round but I didn't care about that and it's light enough it doesn't matter so
它不断旋转着，但我并不在乎这一点。而且它的重量很轻，所以并没有什么关系。
it walks okay it's very wobbly side to side you'll notice though although that
它走路的时候有点摇晃，左右摇晃得很厉害。不过你可能会注意到这一点。
only happens when it walks forwards if I reverse things and walk backwards which
这种情况只会在它向前行走时发生。如果我把顺序颠倒，让它向后行走的话……
I can do just by pulling the stick in the other direction then it's actually much more stable you'll notice his bottom is
我只需把杆子往另一个方向拉，这样它就会稳定得多。你会注意到它的底部……
much more stable than the head was when it was walking the other way
比那只头朝相反方向行走时的状态要稳定得多。
and that is because
因为如此而已。
the head is making it front heavy already but when it pushes all its legs back apart from the one that's in the
头部已经开始向前倾斜了，当它把所有的腿都分开时……
air that
空气
makes it even more front heavy I tried to add Mass to the back by putting a battery on the back outside the
这会让事情变得更加复杂。我试图在设备背面添加质量传感器，就在设备外部的电池位置。
back
后退
and also having some nuts there to add some extra mass it's pretty hard to compensate for the 300 grams hanging so
此外，那里还有一些坚果，可以用来增加额外的体重。不过，要弥补那300克的重量还是相当困难的。
far out the front though
不过，他遥遥领先。
[Music] foreign
[音乐] 异国风情
foreign [Music]
外国音乐
that means at iet's will work if the Star Wars was real life you'd actually be able to send one into battle and
这意味着，只要《星球大战》是真实发生的，你实际上就可以把其中一个角色派往战场上去战斗。
it will walk along it's quite good to know that they're statically stable so it can take one leg off the ground and
它会在那条路上行走。知道它们处于静态稳定状态真是太好了，这样它就可以单腿站立在地面上，继续前进了。
still stand there with it off the ground it doesn't need to put it down again to catch itself because
它静止在那里，脱离了地面的状态，不需要再次将其放下来让它自行恢复平衡——因为……
we all know what happens when at 18s fall over I'm going to publish all the cannon go for this project so
我们都知道，当18岁的年轻人开始堕落时会发生什么。我会公布所有支持这个计划的人的名字。
if you want to have a look at it or build your own you can and that's on GitHub it's totally open source
如果你想要查看它或者自己构建一个版本，是完全可以的。相关代码可以在GitHub上找到，而且它是完全开源的。
so if you want to support me through patreon or YouTube channel membership then those links are in the description below and patrons
所以，如果你希望通过Patreon或订阅YouTube频道来支持我，那么这些链接就在下面的描述中，感谢你的支持！
and YouTube channel members can get access to all the videos up to a week early sneak peeks and
以及YouTube频道成员可以提前一周观看所有视频的预告内容。
pictures of what's coming up and Discord benefits
即将发生的事件图片以及Discord带来的好处